Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004 UA.27.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
News Service Biographical Files
circa 1930s - 2004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. News Service
UA.27.01.0003
183 Linear Feet
The Duke News Service informs the public and the university community about research, programs, and events at Duke. The collection consists of biographical files of Duke University faculty, staff, alumni, and others compiled by the News Service, as well as some photographic materials in separate folders. The files contain primarily clippings and also curricula vitae, photographs, and other printed materials. English.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The News Service Biographical Files were received by the University Archives as transfers in 1991-1995, and 2004.
Historical Note
Formerly known as the News Bureau or News Office. Around 1922, Henry Belk, Class of 1923, was named director of the Trinity News Service. In 1935, the News Service became part of a re-organized Department of Public Relations and Alumni Affairs, with Henry R. Dwire as overall Director. A.A. Wilkinson managed the News Service. Clarence Whitfield was appointed Director of the Bureau of Public Information in 1956, and Director of the Office of Information Services in 1963. This appointment presumably came about as a result of an analysis and appraisal of the University's public relations systems done by the Barton Gillet Company at that time.
The mission of the Duke News Service is to inform the public and the university community about research, programs, and events at Duke; to increase public understanding and appreciation of scholarly contributions made by Duke's faculty and the work of its other employees and students; and to provide media relations and consultative services to faculty and administrators. The Duke News Service works closely with local, national, and international news media, including newspapers, radio and television, magazines, wire services and syndicates.
Collection Overview
The collection consists of biographical files of Duke University faculty, staff, alumni, and others compiled by the News Service. The files contain primarily clippings and also curricula vitae, and other printed materials; most photographic materials were separated into other folders, described below.
Related Material
News Service Subject Files, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
News Service Press Releases and Clippings, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Duke University. News Service; Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University -- Administration
- Abbey, W. D. (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Biographical information - updated
- Abbey, W. D. (Box 123)
  Photograph(s).
- Abbey, W. D. (Box 146)
  Photographic negative(s).
- Abe, Stanley Kenji (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Art and Art History
- Abeles, Paul W. (Box 1)
  Biographical information.
- Abeles, Paul W. (Box 146)
- Abeles, Paul W. (Box 123)
- Abou-Donia, Mohamed B. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pharmacology,Toxicology, 1976-2002
- Abraham, Robert (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pharmacology and Cancer Biology, 1998
- Abraham, Soman (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology and Microbiology, 1999-2001
- Abramson, Murray (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Infectious Diseases, 1998
- Absher, Martha (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pratt
- Abt, Arthur (Box 1)
- Abt, Arthur (Box 123)
- Abt, Arthur (Box 146)
- Acomb, Frances, 1907-1984 (Box 1)
- Adair, Ired (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff
- Adams, Allison B. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Fuqua Business, 1985-1994
- Adams, Anne H. (Box 123)
- Adams, Anne H. (Box 146)
- Adams, Anne H., -1980 (Box 1)
- Adams, Dolph Oliver (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Autopsy Services
- Adams, Donald Keith (Box 123)
- Adams, Donald Keith 1902-1971 (Box 1)
- Adams, Edward L., Jr. (Box 1)
- Adams, Edward L., Jr. (Box 123)
- Adams, Edward L., Jr. (Box 146)
- Adams, James L. (Box 1)
- Adams, James L. (Box 61)
- Adams, Myrna Campbell (Box 123)
- Adams, Myrna Campbell (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Institutional Equity
- Adams, Rex (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Fuqua Business
- Adams, Rex D., Trustee 1995-2001 (Box 115)
- Adams, Richard White (Box 61)
- Adcock, David B. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Univ. Counsel; Health Admin.
- Adcock, John F. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Corp. Controller
- Addoms, Ruth (Box 61)
- Addoms, Ruth (Box 123)
- Addoms, Ruth M. (Box 1)
- Adler, Alexandria (Box 1)
- Aers, David (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English
- Agarwal, Pankaj K. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Computer Science
- Agawu, Kofi V. (Box 1)
- Agnello, Sam (Box 1)
- Agnello, Sam (Box 123)
- Agnello, Sam (Box 146)
- Agres, J.P. (Box 1)
- Aharoni, Yair (Box 61)
- Ahearne, John (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Public Policy
- Ahmann, Dianne (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Microbial Ecology
- Ainsworth, Charles C. (Box 1)
- Ainsworth, Charles C. (Box 146)
- Airall, Zoila E. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Campus Life
- Aitken, Paul W. "Wesley" (Box 123)
- Aitken, Paul W. "Wesley" (Box 146)
- Aitken, Paul W. "Wesley" (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chaplain Service, Retired June, 1987
- Akwari, Onyekwere (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Surgery; Cancer Specialist
- Albert, Mark (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: DUMC
- Alberts, Susan C. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biology/Zoology
- Alden, John R. (Box 123)
- Alden, John R. (Box 146)
- Alden, John R. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Political Science
- Alderman, S. S. (Box 123)
- Alderman, S. S., retired June 6, 1959, Trustee (Box 115)
- Aldrich, John H. (Box 61)
- Aldridge, F.S. (Box 1)
- Aldridge, Fred Soule (Box 123)
- Aldridge, Fred Soule (Box 146)
- Aldridge, Thomas A. (Box 1)
- Aldridge, Thomas A. (Box 146)
- Aldridge, Thomas A., Trustee (Box 115)
- Alexander, Irving (Box 1)
- Alexander, Irving (Box 123)
- Alexander, Irving (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychology
- Alexander, John (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiologist
- Alexander, Kenneth (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Infectius Diseases, Pediatrics
- Alexander, Leo (Box 1)
- Alexander, Susan (Box 61)
- Alexandrou, Dimitri (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Electrical Engineering
- Allard, William K. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Math
- Allen, Clark Lee (Box 1)
- Allen, D.C. (Box 123)
- Allen, D.C. (Box 1)
- Allen, D.C. (Box 146)
- Allen, Devon (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Drama
- Allen, Gay (Box 1)
- Allen, George (Box 123)
- Allen, George (Box 146)
- Allen, George V. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Economics
- Allen, George V., Trustee (Box 115)
- Allen, George V. (Box 1)
- Allen, George V., Trustee (Box 115)
- Allen, Nancy Bates (Box 123)
- Allen, Nancy Bates (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Rheumatology and Immunology
- Allen, Richard Harry (Box 1)
- Allen, Richard Harry (Box 123)
- Allen, Richard Harry (Box 146)
- Alleva, Joe (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Athletics
- Allison, Anne (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cultural Anthropology
- Allison, John A. (Box 111)
- Altrocchi, John Cooley (Box 123)
- Al-Saadawi, Nawal, 2001 (Box 61)
- Alston, Joseph L. (Box 123)
- Alston, Joseph L. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Material Support Services; Minority/Women-Owned Business
- Alston, Wilton D., Trustee (Box 115)
- Alt, Arthur Tilo (Box 123)
- Alt, Arthur Tilo (Box 146)
- Alt, Arthur Tilo (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Germanic Lang. and Lit.
- Altman, Kenneth Wayne (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biomedical Engineering
- Altman, Richard (Box 1)
- Altrocchi, John (Box 1)
- Altrocchi, John Cooley (Box 146)
- Altrocchi, John Cooley (Box 61)
- Altvater, F. Vernon (Box 1)
- Altvater, F. Vernon (Box 123)
- Altvater, F. Vernon (Box 146)
- Alyea, Edwin Pascal (Box 1)
- Alyea, Edwin Pascal (Box 123)
- Amalfitano, Andrea (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: General Medicine - Pediatrics
- Amaya, Marcelino "Marc" (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry. Children's Psychiatric Institute, Umstead Hospital, 1985
- Amore, Thomas (Box 1)
- Amos, Bernard (Box 61)
- Amos, Dennis B. (Box 123)
- Amos, Dennis B. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Microbiology and Immunology, Experimental Surgery
- Amoss, Harold L. (Box 1)
- Anastasion, Nicholas (Box 1)
- Anastasion, Nicholas (Box 146)
- Anderson, Albert, Trustee (Box 115)
- Anderson, Andrew R. (Box 1)
- Anderson, Bill (Box 146)
- Anderson, Carl L. (Box 123)
- Anderson, Carl L. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English. University Ombudsman, Retired Feb. 1990
- Anderson, Charles Roberts (Box 1)
- Anderson, Charles Roberts (Box 146)
- Anderson, David E. (Box 1)
- Anderson, David E. (Box 123)
- Anderson, E. Everett (Box 123)
- Anderson, E. Everett (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Urology, Surgery
- Anderson, Hugh (Box 1)
- Anderson, Hugh (Box 146)
- Anderson, Hugh (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity
- Anderson, James Willis (Box 1)
- Anderson, James Willis (Box 123)
- Anderson, Lewis E. (Box 123)
- Anderson, Lewis E. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Botany
- Anderson, Lewis Edward (Box 1)
- Anderson, Norman (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry; Center for Study of Aging and Human Development
- Anderson, Page A. W. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiology, Pediatrics; Cell Biology
- Anderson, Robert W. (Box 1)
- Anderson, Robert W. (Box 123)
- Anderson, Roger E. (Box 1)
- Anderson, Roger F. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry
- Anderson, W. Banks (Box 123)
- Anderson, W. Banks (Box 146)
- Anderson, W. Banks (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Ophthalmology
- Anderson, William Banks (Box 1)
- Anderson, William Banks (Box 123)
- Anderson, William Blair (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Adolescence Services. McDowell Adolescent Unit
- Anderson, William Blair (Box 123)
- Andreoli, Thomas E. (Box 1)
- Andrewartha, Herbert G. (Box 1)
- Andrews, Edna (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Slavic Languages and Literature
- Andrews, Kree (Box 1)
- Andrews, Kree (Box 146)
- Andrews, Kree (Mrs. Claiborne Andrews) (Box 123)
- Andrews, Lee (Box 1)
- Andrews, Lee (Box 123)
- Andrews, Lee (Box 146)
- Andrews, Samuel W. II (Box 1)
- Andrews, Samuel W. II (Box 123)
- Anlyan, William George (Box 111)
  Biographical information. Chancellor; Head, DUMC; Endowment Trustee, 1950s-1990s
- Annex, Brian (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiology
- Anscher, Mitchell (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiation Oncology
- Antliff, Mark (Box 61)
- Antonovics, Janis (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Botany; University Program in Genetics
- Apgar, Lawrence Clarke (Box 1)
- Appel, Stanley H. (Box 1)
- Appiah, Anthony (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Philosophy
- Applewhite, James W. (Box 111)
  Biographical information. English, 1970s-2000s
- Apte, Mahadev L. (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anthropology
- Aquila, Richard E. (Box 1)
- Aquila, Richard E. (Box 123)
- Aquila, Richard E. (Box 146)
- Aquila, Richard E. (Box 61)
- Arac, Jonathan (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Comparative Literature
- Archer, Ron (Box 61)
- Archibald, Simon (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Research Neurosurgery
- Archie, Dean (Box 1)
- Archie, Dean (Box 146)
- Archie, William C. (Box 1)
- Arcus, David (Box 123)
- Arcus, David (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chapel Music / Organist
- Arena, Jay M. (Box 1)
- Arena, Jay Morris (Box 123)
- Arena, Jay Morris (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pediatrics; Poison Control Center
- Arge, Lars (Box 62)
- Argus, K. Pete (Box 1)
- Argon, Yair (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Microbiology and Immunology; Cell Biology
- Argus, K. Pete (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Civil Engineering
- Armaleo, Daniele (Box 61)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biology
- Armstrong, Brenda Estelle (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiology Pediatrics; Pediatric Cath. Lab
- Armstrong, Clay M. (Box 62)
- Arnett, Edward M. (Box 123)
- Arnett, Edward M. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chairman, Chemistry Dept.
- Arnett, Ned (Box 61)
- Arnold, Ralph (Box 1)
- Artley, John L. (Box 1)
- Artley, John Leslie (Box 123)
- Artley, John Leslie (Box 62)
- Ascher, William Louis (Box 123)
- Ascher, William Louis (Box 62)
- Aschoff, Jurgen W. (Box 1)
- Ashbrook, Arthur G., Jr. (Box 1)
- Ashbrook, Arthur G., Jr. (Box 123)
- Ashbrook, Arthur G., Jr. (Box 146)
- Ashe, John Rainey, Jr. (Box 1)
- Ashmore, Frank L. (Box 1)
- Ashmore, Frank Leon (Box 62)
- Ashmore, Frank Leon (Box 123)
- Ashmore, Frank Leon (Box 146)
- Ashton, Alison Hubbard (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Fuqua
- Ashton, Robert H. (Box 62)
- Ottolenghi, Athos (Box 1)
- Atkinson, Jeanine (Box 62)
- Attebery, Jesse S., Jr. (Box 1)
- Atwood, Theodore W. (Box 1)
- Aubery, Pierre L. (Box 1)
- Aubery, Pierre L. (Box 123)
- Aubery, Pierre L. (Box 146)
- Auerbach, David Alan (Box 1)
- Augustine, George (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurobiology
- Auld, Louis Eugene (Box 1)
- Aumiller, Richard B. (Box 1)
- Austin, Lucy Ann (Box 123)
- Austin, Lucy Ann (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Religious Activities
- Authur, James (Box 62)
- Avery, George S., Jr. (Box 1)
- Aviles, Luis, Jr. (Box 1)
- Aycock, Thomas A. (Box 1)
- Aycock, Thomas A. (Box 123)
- Aycock, Thomas A. (Box 146)
- Ayers, Erle Bingham (Box 1)
- Aylor, Oscar R. (Box 1)
- Aylor, Oscar R. (Box 123)
- Azenberg, Emanuel (Box 62)
- B - Miscellaneous (Box 62)
- Baade, Hans W. (Box 1)
- Baade, Hans W. (Box 123)
- Baade, Hans W. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law
- Babour, George B. (Box 1)
- Babyak, Michael (Box 62)
- Back, Kurt Wolfgang (Box 123)
- Back, Kurt Wolfgang (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sociology
- Badenoch, Ernest (Box 146)
- Baier, Roger W. (Box 1)
- Baier, Roger W. (Box 123)
- Bailey, A. Purnell (Box 111)
  Biographical information. Alumnus
- Bailey, Joseph H. (Box 1)
- Bailey, Joseph R. (Box 123)
- Bailey, Lloyd Richard, Sr. (Box 123)
- Bailey, Lloyd Richard, Sr. (Box 62)
- Baille, John (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Gastroenterology, 1999
- Bain, Barbara (Box 2)
- Bain, Barbara (Box 146)
- Baker, Barbara (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Student Development
- Baker, Bessie (Box 2)
- Baker, Frank (Box 2)
- Baker, Frank (Box 123)
- Baker, Frank (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity, died 10/11/1999
- Baker, Houston (Box 62)
- Baker, John Terrill (Box 62)
- Baker, Kenneth Robert (Box 2)
- Baker, Lee (Box 62)
- Baker, Lennox D. (Box 2)
- Baker, Lennox Dial (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Orthopedic Surgery, died 7/2/1993
- Baker, Mark E. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Imaging, Radiology
- Baker, Maury Davidson (Box 2)
- Baker, Paul Arthur (Box 146)
- Baker, Paul Arthur (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geology
- Baker, Roger (Box 123)
- Baker, Roger (Box 146)
- Baker, Roger (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology
- Baker, Roger D. (Box 2)
- Baldwin, Alice M. (Box 2)
- Baldwin, Steven (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chemistry
- Baley, James A. (Box 2)
- Baligh, Helmy Hamdollah (Box 123)
- Baligh, Helmy Hamdollah (Box 62)
- Ball, David (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Drama Program; English
- Ball, M. Margaret (Box 123)
- Ball, M. Margaret (Box 146)
- Ball, M. Margaret (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Woman's College; Political Science
- Ball, Margaret (Box 2)
- Ballantyne, Robert Hubbard (Box 123)
- Ballantyne, Robert Hubbard (Box 146)
- Ballantyne, Robert Hubbard (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Education
- Ballard, Bruce W. (Box 2)
- Balleisen, Edward J. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: History
- Banham, Katharine May (Box 62)
- Banham, Katharine May (Box 2)
- Banks, Darryl (Box 62)
- Banks, Eugene (Box 2)
- Barber, James David (Box 62)
- Barber, James David (Box 111)
  Biographical information. Political Science, 1972-1999
- Barber, Richard Trumpter (Box 123)
- Barber, Richard Trumpter (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Zoology; Marine Lab
- Barefoot, John (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Psychology
- Barefoot, Sherwood W. (Box 2)
- Barefoot, Sherwood W. (Box 123)
- Barker, Ruth E. (Box 2)
- Barker, Ruth E. (Box 123)
- Barlow, Norman Howard (Box 2)
- Barnes, Evelyn (Box 2)
- Barnes, J. Foster (Box 2)
- Barnes, James Foster (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke Chapel Choir, died 2/9/1956
- Barnes, Myrtle Preyer (Box 2)
- Barnes, Ralph Willet, Jr. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Instructor, Electrical Engineering
- Barnes, Robert D. (Box 2)
- Barnes, Robert D. (Box 123)
- Barnes, Robert H. (Box 2)
- Barnes, Robert L. (Box 123)
- Barnes, Robert L. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry and Environmental Studies
- Barnes, Samuel Henry, Trustee 1989- (Box 115)
- Barnhardt, J. H., Trustee (Box 115)
- Barnhart, Francis E. (Box 2)
- Barnhart, Francis E. (Box 123)
- Barnhart, Francis E. (Box 146)
- Barr, Roger C. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biomedical Engineering; Pediatrics
- Barr, Roger C. (Box 123)
- Barre, Lt. Col. Louis Albin, III (Box 123)
- Barre, Lt. Col. Louis Albin, III (Box 146)
- Barre, Lt. Col. Louis Albin, III (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Aerospace Studies
- Barringer, Emma B. (Mrs. Earl Brian) (Box 125)
- Barringer, Thad Jones (Box 62)
- Barringer, Thad Jones (Box 123)
- Barringer, Thad Jones (Box 146)
- Barrow, John C. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Clinical Psychiatry
- Barry, William F. (Box 2)
- Bartlet, M. Elizabeth C. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Music
- Bartlett, Frederick (Box 146)
- Bartlett, John A. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine
- Bartlett, Katharine T. (Box 62)
- Bartlett, Richard J. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medied Research Neurology
- Bartlett, Robert B. (Box 2)
- Bartlett, Robert C. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Physical Therapy
- Barton, Furman W. (Box 123)
- Barton, Furman W. (Box 146)
- Barton, Furman W. (Box 62)
- Basefsky, Stuart M. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Library: Public Documents and Maps
- Basgall, Monte (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Science Writer
- Bashore, Thomas Michael (Box 62)
- Baskin, Yvonne (Box 123)
- Baskin, Yvonne (Box 146)
- Baskin, Yvonne (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: DUMC, Public Relations
- Bass, Reiner (Box 2)
- Bassett, Frank Houston, III (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Orthopedic Surgery
- Bassett, Frank Houston, III (Box 123)
- Bassett, John Spencer (Box 2)
- Bassett, Robert V. R., Jr. (Box 2)
- Bast, Robert C., Jr. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Hematology and Medical Oncology; Comprehensive Cancer Center
- Bastia, Deepak (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Microbiology
- Batchelor, Wayne (Box 62)
- Bateman, Bruce H. (Box 62)
- Bates, Margaret (Box 123)
- Bates, Margaret (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Academic Programs and Facilities
- Bates, Robert Hinricks (Box 62)
- Battle, Joseph (Box 62)
- Baugh, Philip Jackson "Jack" (Box 123)
- Baugh, Philip Jackson "Jack", Trustee 1988- (Box 115)
- Baugh, Phillip Jackson (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Univ. Trustee
- Baum, Paul Franklin (Box 2)
- Baum, Walter P. (Box 2)
- Baunach, Warren E. (Box 123)
- Baunach, Warren E. (Box 62)
- Baxley, John V. (Box 2)
- Baxley, John Virgil (Box 123)
- Baxter, Lawrence G. (Box 123)
- Baxter, Lawrence G. (Box 62)
- Baylin, George (Box 123)
- Baylin, George (Box 146)
- Baylin, George J. (Box 2)
- Baylis, Charles A. (Box 2)
- Baylis, Charles A. (Box 123)
- Baylis, Charles A. (Box 62)
- Baysinger, Reaves H. (Box 2)
- Bazinsky, Jordan, Trustee (Box 115)
- Beach, W. Waldo (Box 2)
- Beach, William Waldo (Box 123)
- Beach, William Waldo (Box 146)
- Beach, William Waldo (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity (retired 9/1/1986), died 1/11/2001
- Beal, James A. (Box 2)
- Beale, Sara Sun (Box 123)
- Beale, Sara Sun (Box 62)
- Beale, Tom (Box 62)
- Beall (Ting-Beall), Hie Ping (Box 62)
- Beals, Richard (Box 2)
- Bear, Warren C. (Box 2)
- Beard, Dorothy Waters (Box 123)
- Beard, Dorothy Waters (Box 146)
- Beard, Dorothy Waters (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Surgery, DUMC
- Beard, Joseph W. (Box 2)
- Beard, Joseph Willis (Box 123)
- Beard, Joseph Willis (Box 146)
- Beard, Joseph Willis (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Surgery; Virology
- Bearman, Dale Michael (Box 2)
- Beatty, I. Croom (Box 2)
- Beauchamp, Carole A. (Box 123)
- Beauchamp, Carole A. (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Policy Sciences and Public Affairs
- Beaudreau, George S. (Box 2)
- Becker, R. Frederick (Box 2)
- Becker, Roland Frederick (Box 62)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anatomy
- Beckton, Charles L. (Box 123)
- Beckton, Charles L. (Box 63)
- Beckum, Leonard C. (Box 123)
- Beckum, Leonard C. (Box 62)
- Beckwith, Sarah T. (Box 63)
- Bedard, Evelyn M. (Box 123)
- Bedard, Evelyn M. (Box 146)
- Bedard, Evelyn M. (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Nursing
- Beddingfield, Edgar T. (Box 63)
- Beese, Lorena S. (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biochemistry
- Behar, Victor S. (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine; Cardiovascular Lab
- Behn, Robert Dietrich (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sanford Institute
- Behringer, Robert P. (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Physics
- Beidelman, Thomas Owen (Box 63)
- Bejan, Adrian (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Mechanical Engineering and Material Science
- Bell, David Fowler, III (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Romance Languages
- Bell, Gordon E. (Box 2)
- Bell, Gordon E. (Box 146)
- Bell, James Ardrey, Trustee (Box 115)
- Bell, Joanne M. (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Research
- Bell, Joseph C. (Box 63)
- Bell, Robert M. (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biochemistry; Comprehensive Cancer Center
- Bell, W. B., Trustee (Box 115)
- Bell, Wilhelmina (Box 2)
- Bell, William V. (Box 63)
- Bellows, Rowland T. (Box 2)
- Belvin, James A., Jr. (Box 123)
- Belvin, James A., Jr. (Box 63)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Undergraduate Financial Aid
- Benedict, Barbara (Box 2)
- Benedict, Barbara A. (Box 123)